["Pomp D D D D D D
二零二二年昆明市初中学业水平考试英语听力部分。第一节：听句子，选出与所听句子内容相符的图画。听音前，你有十秒钟的读题时间。注意听两遍。
Op. No. in No.
16 in 16 2 No.
第二节：根据所听到的句子，选出最恰当的应答语。听音前，你有十秒钟的读题时间。注意听两遍。
2 2 2 Major, No.
D Major, Op.
16 2 Major, 9.
It's necessary to wash hands in the right way.
10. Would you mind my closing the door?
11. Which teacher do you like best?
第三节：听对话及问题，选择最佳答案。听音前，你有十秒钟的读题时间。注意听两遍。
I like Mr.
best. He teaches us math, and he can always make it fun.
12. I can't find my key.
Where is it?
It's in the bookcase next to the ruler.
13. What did you do last weekend?
I just stayed at home and didn't do anything on Saturday, and I went to the art
museum on Sunday.
What did the boy do on Sunday?
What did you do last weekend?
just stayed at home and didn't do anything on Saturday, and I went to the art museum
on Sunday. 18.
did the boy do on Sunday?
14. What's the date today, It's June the 18th.
The exams are over today.
I'm going to see a movie the day after tomorrow.
Question. When is Mike going to see a movie?
15. What's the date today,
It's June the 18th.
The exams are over today.
I'm going to see a movie the day after tomorrow.
Question. When is Mike going to see a movie?
15. Hi, Tom.
How do you learn English?
I usually read English books.
It can help me to learn some useful sentences.
Question. How does Tom learn English?
usually read English books.
It can help me to learn some useful sentences.
Question. How does Tom learn English?
第四节听短文，根据短文内容回答问题。听音前，你有十五秒钟的读题时间，注意听三遍。
Tom learn English?
In China, school gardening is now very popular.
The parents and the teachers all think these hands -on lessons are interesting and
useful. The students are excited about the gardening lessons too.
The lessons give them a new way of learning and help them relax.
The students don't have to sit at their desks all day.
They have a chance to move outside and get their hands dirty.
The teachers teach gardening with a purpose.
In gardens, they ask the students to watch carefully so that the students can see
the beginning, the middle, and the end of the project.
However, some schools don't have enough space for a garden.
The students can then go to city gardens for help.
Gardening is an important subject,
many teachers say.
It not only lets the students know where our food comes from, but also makes them
have more respect for nature.
In China, school gardening is now very popular.
The parents and the teachers all think these hands -on lessons are interesting and
useful. The students are excited about the gardening lessons too.
The lessons give them a new way of learning and help them relax.
The students don't have to sit at their desks all day.
They have a chance to move outside and get their hands dirty.
The teachers teach gardening with a purpose.
In gardens, they ask the students to watch carefully so that the students can see
the beginning, the middle, and the end of the project.
However, some schools don't have enough space for a garden.
The students can then go to city gardens for help.
Gardening is an important subject, many teachers say.
It not only lets the students know where our food comes from, but also makes them
have more respect for nature.
In China, school gardening is now very popular.
The parents and the teachers all think these hands -on lessons are interesting and
useful. The students are excited about the gardening lessons too.
The lessons give them a new way of learning and help them relax.
The students don't have to sit at their desks all day.
They have a chance to move outside and get their hands dirty.
The teachers teach gardening with a purpose.
In gardens, they ask the students to watch carefully so that the students can see
the beginning, the middle, and the end of the project.
However, some schools don't have enough space for a garden.
The students can then go to city gardens for help.
Gardening is an important subject,
many teachers say.
It not only lets the students know where our food comes from, but also makes them
have more respect for nature.
concludes Thank
听力测试到此结束。